{
"question": "作文",
"answer": "さくぶん"
},
{
"question": "紅茶",
"answer": "こうちゃ"
},
{
"question": "家庭",
"answer": "かてい"
},
{
"question": "野菜",
"answer": "やさい"
},
{
"question": "風呂",
"answer": "ふろ"
},
{
"question": "玄関",
"answer": "げんかん"
},
{
"question": "地下鉄",
"answer": "ちかてつ"
},
{
"question": "鼻",
"answer": "はな"
},
{
"question": "緑",
"answer": "みどり"
},
{
"question": "昼",
"answer": "ひる"
},
{
"question": "西",
"answer": "にし"
},
{
"question": "白",
"answer": "しろ"
},
{
"question": "洗濯",
"answer": "せんたく"
},
{
"question": "冷蔵庫",
"answer": "れいぞうこ"
},
{
"question": "南",
"answer": "みなみ"
},
{
"question": "火曜日",
"answer": "かようび"
},
{
"question": "北",
"answer": "きた"
},
{
"question": "茶色",
"answer": "ちゃいろ"
},
{
"question": "黒",
"answer": "くろ"
},
{
"question": "喫茶店",
"answer": "きっさてん"
},
